Inventory of the Wesleyan Spirits Records, 1981 - 2005
Wesleyan Spirits Records, 1981 - 2005
Special Collections & Archives, Wesleyan University
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)
1000-77
1.5
3
The Wesleyan Spirits are an all-male a capella vocal group at Wesleyan.
The Wesleyan Spirits Records include documentation of the group's activities and travels.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisitions Information
Donated by members of the Wesleyan Spirits, circa 1999-2006.
Historical Note
The Wesleyan Spirits are an all-male a capella vocal group at Wesleyan.
Collection Overview
The Wesleyan Spirits Records include documentation of the group's activities and travels. Materials are periodically added by members of the Wesleyan Spirits.
The materials have been inventoried but not arranged.
Online Catalog Headings
These and related materials may be found under the following headings in online catalogs.
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Students.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Songs and music.; Choruses, Secular (Men’s voices), Unaccompanied.; Students’ songs--Connecticut--Middletown.
Detailed Description of the Collection
  - Membership (Box 1)
  - Music and arrangements
  - Budget
  - Photographs
  - History
  - Correspondence
  - Recordings information
  - Spring Break journals, 2001-2003 (Box 2)
    Note: Three volumes.
  - Japan Tour journal, 2003
  - Applications, fall 2004
  - Spring Break journal, 2005
  - Correspondence (1 card) with 4 photos
  - 2003-2005 audition form
  - Spirit history, 2001-2005
  - Photographs
  - Awards
  - Inter-Spirit correspondence
  - Recording information (old)
  - Wesleyan Songbook, first edition, 1901
  - Japan tour, 2003 (Box 3)
    Note: includes video, DVD, photographs, clippings, and other materials.